[
    {
        "family": 12,
        "modelo": "iPhone 12",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A14 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.1 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP Dual"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "64 GB",
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_azul/ip12_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_azul/ip12_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_azul/ip12_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_azul/ip12_blue_sideUp.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "##faf2f1",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_blanco/ip12_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_blanco/ip12_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_blanco/ip12_white_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_blanco/ip12_white_sideUp.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_negro/ip12_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_negro/ip12_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_negro/ip12_black_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_negro/ip12_black_sideUp.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#B88CC4",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_purpura/ip12_purple_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_purpura/ip12_purple_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_purpura/ip12_purple_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_purpura/ip12_purple_sideUp.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#CE3B46",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_rojo/ip12_red_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_rojo/ip12_red_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_rojo/ip12_red_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_rojo/ip12_red_sideUp.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#4ACFAC",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_verde/ip12_green_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_verde/ip12_green_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_verde/ip12_green_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip12/ip12_verde/ip12_green_sideUp.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 12,
        "modelo": "iPhone 12 Pro",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A14 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.1 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {

                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_superposition.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 12,
        "modelo": "iPhone 12 Pro Max",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A14 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.1 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_azul/ip12_proMax_blue_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_negro/ip12_proMax_black_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_oro/ip12_proMax_gold_superposition.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_sideUp.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip12_pro_proMax/ip12_pro_plata/ip12_proMax_silver_superposition.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 13,
        "modelo": "iPhone 13",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A15 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.23 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP Dual"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_azul/ip13_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_azul/ip13_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_azul/ip13_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_azul/ip13_blue_sideButton.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_azul/ip13_blue_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_blanco/ip13_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_blanco/ip13_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_blanco/ip13_white_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_blanco/ip13_white_sideButton.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_blanco/ip13_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#101424",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_medianoche/ip13_midnight_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_medianoche/ip13_midnight_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_medianoche/ip13_midnight_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_medianoche/ip13_midnight_sideButton.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_medianoche/ip13_midnight_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e62b38",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rojo/ip13_red_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rojo/ip13_red_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rojo/ip13_red_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rojo/ip13_red_sideButton.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rojo/ip13_red_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffddd6",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rosa/ip13_pink_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rosa/ip13_pink_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rosa/ip13_pink_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rosa/ip13_pink_sideButton.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13/ip13_rosa/ip13_pink_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 13,
        "modelo": "iPhone 13 Pro",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A15 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.23 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#4c4a46",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_backSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 13,
        "modelo": "iPhone 13 Pro Max",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A15 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.23 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagenColoresFamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_azul/ip13_pro_blue_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#4c4a46",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_grafito/ip13_pro_graphite_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_oro/ip13_pro_gold_backSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_frontSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip13_pro_proMax/ip13_pro_plata/ip13_pro_silver_backSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 14,
        "modelo": "iPhone 14",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A15 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.23 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP Dual"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                   
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e9e3eb",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#101424",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e62b38",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 14,
        "modelo": "iPhone 14 Plus",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A15 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.23 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP Dual"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_blanco/ip14_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e9e3eb",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_purpura/ip14_purple_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_azul/ip14_blue_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#101424",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_medianoche/ip14_midnight_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e62b38",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_backAndSide.webp",
                "imgSpecial": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14/ip14_rojo/ip14_red_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 14,
        "modelo": "iPhone 14 Pro",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A16 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.46 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e9e3eb",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_frontSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 14,
        "modelo": "iPhone 14 Pro Max",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A16 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.46 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "Conector Lightning",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_negro/ip14_pro_black_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_plata/ip14_pro_silver_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffecd2",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_oro/ip14_pro_gold_frontSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#e9e3eb",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_backSide.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip14_pro/ip14_pro_violeta/ip14_pro_violet_frontSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 15,
        "modelo": "iPhone 15",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A16 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.46 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "USB-C",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": []
    },
    {
        "family": 15,
        "modelo": "iPhone 15 Plus",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A16 Bionic",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.46 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "USB-C",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": []
    },
    {
        "family": 15,
        "modelo": "iPhone 15 Pro",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A17 Pro",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.70 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "128 GB",
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.1 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "USB-C",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#607D8B",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#FFFFFF",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#000000",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#B0B0B0",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_rightSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 15,
        "modelo": "iPhone 15 Pro Max",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "A17 Pro",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 6,
            "potencia": "3.70 GHz"
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": "48 MP + 12 MP + 12 MP"
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": "12 MP"
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [
            "256 GB",
            "512 GB",
            "1 TB"
        ],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": "6.7 pulgadas"
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "IP68 (hasta 6 metros por 30 minutos)",
            "tipo_sim": [
                "Dual SIM (Nano-SIM y eSIM)",
                "Soporte para SIM física y eSIM"
            ],
            "nfc": true,
            "pin_carga": "USB-C",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#607D8B",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_azul_titanio/ip15_pro_blueTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#FFFFFF",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_blanco_titanio/ip15_pro_whiteTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#000000",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_negro_titanio/ip15_pro_blackTitanium_rightSide.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#B0B0B0",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_camera.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip15_pro_max/ip15_pro_titanio/ip15_pro_titanium_rightSide.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 16,
        "modelo": "iPhone 16",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 0,
            "potencia": ""
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": ""
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": ""
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": ""
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "",
            "tipo_sim": [],
            "nfc": false,
            "pin_carga": "",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffddd6",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#9fc6c4",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 16,
        "modelo": "iPhone 16 Plus",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 0,
            "potencia": ""
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": ""
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": ""
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": ""
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "",
            "tipo_sim": [],
            "nfc": false,
            "pin_carga": "",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#044d93",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_azul/ip16_blue_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_blanco/ip16_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_negro/ip16_black_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#ffddd6",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_rosa/ip16_pink_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#9fc6c4",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16/ip16_verde/ip16_green_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 16,
        "modelo": "iPhone 16 Pro",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 0,
            "potencia": ""
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": ""
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": ""
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": ""
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "",
            "tipo_sim": [],
            "nfc": false,
            "pin_carga": "",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#ececec",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#D2B48C",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#A6A6A6",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#17111a",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "family": 16,
        "modelo": "iPhone 16 Pro Max",
        "procesador": {
            "tipo": "",
            "cantidad_nucleos": 0,
            "potencia": ""
        },
        "camara": {
            "trasera": {
                "resolucion": ""
            },
            "frontal": {
                "resolucion": ""
            }
        },
        "almacenamiento": [],
        "pantalla": {
            "medidas": ""
        },
        "otros": {
            "resistente_agua_polvo": "",
            "tipo_sim": [],
            "nfc": false,
            "pin_carga": "",
            "viene_con_cargador": false
        },
        "imagencoloresfamilia": " ",
        "imagenes": [
            {
                "imgColor": "#FFFFFF",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_blanco/ip16_proMax_white_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#D2B48C",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_desierto_titanio/ip16_proMax_desertTitanium_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#A6A6A6",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_titanio_natural/ip16_proMax_naturalTitanium_special.webp"
            },
            {
                "imgColor": "#000000",
                "imgFront": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_front.webp",
                "imgBack": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_back.webp",
                "imgCamera": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_screen.webp",
                "imgSide": "/iphonesAllPictures/ip16_pro_proMax/ip16_pro_max_negro/ip16_proMax_black_special.webp"
            }
        ]
    }
]